Now, as I have told you, you have to forgive yourself and you have to forgive others.
كما ذكرت، عليك أن تسامح نفسك وعليك أن تسامح الآخرين.
It's very important.
هذا مهم جدًا.
What you can do now is just to put both your hands towards me like this.
ما يمكنك فعله الآن هو أن تضع يديك تجاهي هكذا.
Just like this, simple like this.
تماماً هكذا، ببساطة هكذا.
The way you do for namaz, just like that.
كما تفعل وقت الدعاء هكذا تمامًا.
Alright.
حسناً.
Please again forgive yourself and forgive everyone else.
أرجوك سامح نفسك مجددًا، و سامح الآخرين.
Now you can bend your head.
الآن، أحنِ رأسك.
And put your left hand on top of your fontanel bone area which was the soft bone in your childhood.
و ضع يدك اليسرى فوق منطقة عظم اليافوخ، وهي العظمة التي كانت لينة في طفولتك.
On top and above.
فوق رأسك وأعلى.
Now see if there is cool or hot breeze coming out of your fontanel bone area.
الآن، انظر إن كان هناك نسمة هواء باردة أو ساخنة تخرج من منطقة عظم اليافوخ.
Please move your hand.
حرّك يدك.
Have faith in yourself, have faith.
ثق بنفسك، ثق بنفسك.
Forgive yourself.
سامح نفسك.
Alright.
حسناً.
Now please put your left hand towards me and with the right hand please see, bend your head,
الآن، من فضلك، ضع يدك اليسرى تجاهي، و احنِ رأسك.
please see if there is a cool breeze coming out of your fontanel bone area.
من فضلك، انظر إن كان هناك نسمة هواء باردة قادمة من منطقة عظم اليافوخ.
If it is hot air, then you have not forgiven either yourself or others.
إن كان هواء ساخنا ، فأنت لم تسامح نفسك أو الآخرين.
So please do that now.
لذا من فضلك، افعل ذلك الآن.
Alright.
حسناً.
Now again once more put your right hand towards me like this open and see with your left hand,
الآن، مرة أخرى، ضع يدك اليمني تجاهي هكذا وانظر بيدك اليسرى
bend your head and see for yourself if there is a cool or a hot breeze coming out of your fontanel bone area.
احنِ رأسك وانظر بنفسك إن كان هناك نسمة هواء باردة أو ساخنة قادمة من منطقة عظم اليافوخ.
Now please put your both the hands towards me
الآن، من فضلك، ضع كلتا يديك تجاهي
and please don't think.
و من فضلك، لا تفكر
Can you do that?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
Don't think.
لا تفكر.
Now, please see if you are getting cool or hot breeze on your fingertips.
الآن، من فضلك، انظر إن كنت تشعر بنسيم بارد أو ساخن على أطراف أصابعك.
Or you are getting it on your palms.
أو إن كنت تشعر به على راحتي يديك.
Or out of your fontanel bone area.
أو خارج منطقة عظم اليافوخ
Anywhere if you are getting cool or hot breeze, please raise your hands.
أو إن كنت تشعر بنسيم بارد أو ساخن علي أي جزء من جسدك، من فضلك ارفع يديك
Please raise your hands.
من فضلك ارفع يديك.
You’re all have become sufis now, congratulations.
لقد أصبحتم جميعًا متصوفيين الآن، أهنئكم.
May God bless you.
بارك الله فيكم.
Turkey is a very divine place.
تركيا مكان روحاني للغاية.
In such a  short time you got your realisation.
في وقت قصير جدًا، حصلتم علي تحقيق الذات.
Don't doubt it please.
لا تشكوا في ذلك من فضلكم.
All right take down your hands.
حسناً، اخفضوا أيديكم.
I saw more ladies in the airport maybe the men were busy but I want men also to become
رأيت غالبية الحضور من السيدات في المطار، ربما كان الرجال مشغولون لكنني أريد أن يحصل الرجال أيضًا
realised souls, very important.
علي تحقيق الذات، وهذا أمر مهم جدًا.
Now you will know what is pure love, pure compassion.
الآن ستعرفون ما هو الحب النقي، الرحمة النقية.
Because this is the power of divine compassion, divine love.
لأن هذه هي قوة الرحمة الإلهية، الحب الإلهي.
May God bless you all.
بارك الله فيكم جميعاً.